deliverawaydebt.com 2011-05-26

# Privacy

**Privacy**  
The privacy of the visitors to Deliverawaydebt is important. At Deliverawaydebt, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use visit Deliverawaydebt, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

**Log Files**  
As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as Comcast or AT&T), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site.We also use third party advertisements on Deliverawaydebt to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies, DART cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. Use of cookies is generally used for geotargeting purposes or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited. The use of DART cookies enables advertisers such as Google Adsense to serve ads based on your visit and your visits to other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network [privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

**RSS and Email Subscriptions**  
this website records information about how people access our RSS feeds, but does not collect any personally identifying information from or about our RSS subscribers. This website’s feed services collect the e-mail addresses of individuals that subscribe to our RSS feed via e-mail. Individual information about subscribers to this website’s feed is held in strict confidence; we will not release or disclose any specific subscriber information under any circumstances, unless required by law. Aggregated information stripped of any personally identifiable information may be disclosed.

**Comments**  
We reserve the right to edit or remove comments left on this website at our sole discretion. If provided, site URLs (along with all other information) are published along with comments. Commentator email addresses are required with the submission of comments but are not disclosed, as long as the commentator does not enter their e-mail address directly into the main comment area in addition to the box supplied for their e-mail address.

**External Links**  
This web site contains links to other external websites not owned by the owner of this website. We cannot control how your personal information is used on these other websites, so please be sure to see how they use your information by consulting their privacy policies respectively.

**Article by[Jeff Kosola](http://deliverawaydebt.com/about-2/)**

**[DeliverAwayDebt](http://deliverawaydebt.com/)** is designed to help people along the journey toward "Debt Freedom". I use my battle against debt to demonstrate anyone with enough passion and motivation can blast away debt. My net worth is updated monthly and all my [Pizza Delivery](http://deliverawaydebt.com/pizza-delivery) earnings are tracked. These are posted to demonstrate that **YOU CAN** eliminate your own debt. It will take some work, but nothing in life that matters is easy. 

Here are **3 Free ways** to receive updates from **DeliverAwayDebt**. Subscribe to the [RSS Feed](http://feeds.feedburner.com/deliverawaydebt). Subscribe by [Email](http://feedburner.google.com/fb/a/mailverify?uri=Deliverawaydebt&loc=en_US). Or Follow me on [Twitter](http://twitter.com/deliverawaydebt)

Read more from **DeliverAwayDebt** in the **[Archives](http://deliverawaydebt.com/archives/)**.
